Store object's in Versions format
----------------------------------
Store object's as versions format
Create S3 bucket by making it public.
Enable versioning.
Upload text document with one line and make it public.
Upload the same text document by adding one more line and make it public.(can see both versions)

Recover from accidental deletion
----------------------------------
Delete object.
Recover by deleting delete marker.
If you delete text document, can recover it. But if you delete individual versions,you cann't recover.